short episode where I talk about three things, what's on my mind this week, recommended
reading and something fun. This is the show that helps you automate your business
so you can take time off, worry free, and hopefully this curation will help you think
more about your systems. Systems. I'm your host, Joe Casabona, and here's what's
When does implementation hinder you?
I'm doing Kyle Adams newsletter Power Up cohort, and it's been
fantastic. As a result, I spent a lot of time over the last 10 days working on a
new welcome sequence and just cleaning up the near 10 years at this point, cruft
in my kit account.
I thought long and hard about this experience, how everything is implemented and
email a day, and I wanted to make sure everything got to delivered in the order in
which I thought it would be.
Now, I believe my bias towards action is good. I rarely get stuck in the
just need to do it. Phase I'm usually doing.
Where I do get stuck is the doing it phase, though
I consider the implementation and the long-term ramifications, even if something
is just an experiment, and maybe in this case
I should have spent
a bunch of time on the implementation, but the technical debt of over-engineering
implementations of the past that I didn't do or use very much
hindered me. An example is last week I rolled out a new lead magnet and I changed
the process a little bit and I really thought about the implementation
or I build interesting creative, but sometimes over complicated things.
And part of it is the tension of wanting to launch quickly
with the phrase I've been saying for a long time.
that takes time. Rushing to pick a platform or a tool is going to take time. The
problem is
I spend a bunch of time implementing and then usually have to change something anyway,
the truth is that there needs to be some balance.
Occam's razor is another idea I think about all the time. It's often quoted as the
simplest solution is the right one or the best one,
but it's actually more nuanced than that. It's that
our solutions to problems
should be constructed with the smallest possible set of elements.
simplest solution is the best one. But again, that's not entirely true.
It's it's actually the smallest possible set of elements. And when I'm trying to
there.
But something that I need to remember that you need to remember as you are building
out your systems
is that when we build online,
very little is permanent.
Yes, something you tweeted near 20 years ago,
could resurface at any moment,
but the system you build
can be iterated on. It's not like building a skyscraper
iteration is our friend.
I'm really good at doing that part for other people.
Let's get you set up as quickly and as easily as possible in a way that's not going
to overwhelm you,
but I need to be better about doing it for myself.
I am not scared of the systems and I like experimenting, and that
could lead to over-engineering and ultimately me focusing too much on the implementing
part
in a way where it becomes a blocker.
So that's what I'm thinking about this week. I would love your thoughts on that.
If you go to streamlined feedback.com, you can write into the show.
But let's move on to recommended reading.
This is an article from FanGraphs called The Haters All Star Game. I'm a huge baseball
fan
even though this year it was like a Vince McMahon's wet dream.
but I really
love watching the Allstar game. I'm, I'm gonna have to probably put an explicit warning
players come together and have fun and celebrate their accomplishments and what is
a very long season.
once the season resumes there, there may be bitter rivalries,
right? The rivalries are for the fans.
Players should not hate each other because of the team that they're on.
it was seeing Philadelphia Phillies fans, boo,
all of the non Phillies players.
This is supposed to be a jovial celebration of the best in the game, the best and
brightest.
And of course, Philly,
the city that threw batteries at Santa Claus couldn't abide by that. But
the reason I like this article, I'm linking the haters all-star game,
is because it got me thinking, should that annoy me?
Isn't Philly just being Philly?
It didn't seem to annoy my guy, Ben Rice or Home Run Derby winner, Jordan Walker
or even William Contrera, someone who famously gets annoyed by everything. The dude
starts more fights than Connor McGregor.
that professional athletes get paid to play a game,
I need to remember that the fans are going to be the fans.
And for Philly, that means doggedly defending your home from outsiders,
So I really liked that article.
Love to Philly fans.
you might, if you watched or listened to last week's episode, you might be thinking
The Odyssey again.
Joe, you recommended The Odyssey last week,
and that is true,
but this is the Odyssey in one minute.
I am so excited for this movie, especially after finishing the book earlier this
month,
in exactly 60 seconds
in Dactylic Hexter, which is the,
the melody of the epic poem, right? That's like how the Iliad and the Odyssey
It is so dope
and I have listened to it
a thousand times. Love it. Highly recommend it, watch it a million times. Don't be
surprised if next week I recommend the Odyssey of the movie again.
I'll try much like House of the Dragon to not keep recommending it.
All right, and automations
of the week,
the automation of the week this week is hunting down opt-ins with Claude. As I mentioned
in on My Mind,
I've been spending a lot of time on my mailing list and
how it delivers my vast amount of lead magnets
and content.
I also have tons of opt-in pages across multiple websites. And as I have been reworking
my lead magnets, my welcome sequence, my delivery mechanisms, I don't want any of
those pages or forms or automations to lead to a dead end. So
instead of doing a hand done audit,
I uploaded exports of all of my pages from my websites, any redirects I had from
so that Claude can see what I've got going on in my account. I even had it 'cause
it can't,
the MCP doesn't expose,
kit automations. And so I also had Claude like go out to the browser and have a look
at all of my automations,
and I got a full report on active forms, the ones that are working well, and all
I will redirect to a page with information about the talk.
So I was able to
redirect, delete, and consolidate.
And now Kit is squeaky clean. I have a better
understanding of how everything is delivered, and it's just a lot cleaner.
This would've been an incredibly time consuming for me
or expensive task for my VA without Claude.
It's been incredible seeing what insights and data I can grab thanks to the connectors
and automation tools that exist within the LLM. And that's why this is my automation
of the week. It's, it wasn't a,
I set this up and now it's going to run routinely, but it was a, here's all of the
data that I have sift through it so that I don't have to sift through it.
That is another form of automation
and it was hugely helpful
in this instance.
All of this, let me focus my time where it matters most. Helping you build better
systems so you can step away from your business without worrying. And
because I was able to free up some time thanks to Claude
over the past week, I took most of the afternoon off to see my daughter perform.
fully be present
because I was able to do the work I had to get done,
done.
But that's it for this episode of the Streamlined Solopreneur and the Friday Wrap.
If you enjoyed this, consider joining my newsletter at streamlined fm slash wrap.
You'll get insights and thoughts and ideas about how to build better systems for
yourself so that you
can confidently
step away from your business without worrying.
Thanks so much for listening, and until next time, I hope you find some space in